Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪No one left to lean on♪
♪لم يبق أحد يمكن الاعتماد عليه♪
♪No way out, no place to run♪
♪لا مخرج، لا مكان للهروب♪
♪Tears held back inside my eyes♪
♪الدموع محصورة في عيني♪
♪I run against the wind and time♪
♪أركض ضد الريح والوقت♪
♪Loved and lost, regrets remain♪
♪ محبوبون وضائعون، والندم يبقى ♪
♪But tears fall down like gentle rain♪
♪ولكن الدموع تسقط مثل المطر اللطيف♪
♪I look up strong, I grow with pride♪
♪أنظر إلى الأعلى بقوة، وأنمو بفخر♪
♪Living life with heart untied♪
♪عيش الحياة بقلب غير مقيد♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪التمسك بقوة♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪الإيمان المتقد الذي أعطيته♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪شفاء الجروح التي نقشها القدر♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪هذا النور داخل روحي المضطربة♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪حياة واحدة للعيش، وهدف نهائي واحد♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪سأحب بشجاعة، بوحشية وحرية♪
♪Break through the noise, let them hear me♪
♪اخترق الضوضاء، دعهم يسمعونني♪
♪Holding tight♪
♪التمسك بقوة♪
♪The burning faith you gave♪
♪الإيمان المتقد الذي أعطيته♪
♪Healing wounds that fate engraved♪
♪شفاء الجروح التي نقشها القدر♪
♪That light inside my restless soul♪
♪هذا النور داخل روحي المضطربة♪
♪One life to live, one final goal♪
♪حياة واحدة للعيش، وهدف نهائي واحد♪
♪I'll love with courage, wild and free♪
♪سأحب بشجاعة، بوحشية وحرية♪
♪Break through the noise, let them hear me♪
♪اخترق الضوضاء، دعهم يسمعونني♪
=Dragon King's Decree=
=مرسوم ملك التنين=
=Episode 18=
=الحلقة 18=
I heard from the elders
سمعت من الشيوخ
that you finally recognized
أنك تعرفت عليه أخيرا
your place and duty beneath the Tree of Life.
مكانك وواجبك تحت شجرة الحياة.
No matter whether Moshang or I become Dragon King,
بغض النظر عما إذا أصبح موشانغ أو أنا ملك التنين،
we will never forget
لن ننسى أبدا
the mission we were born with.
الرسالة التي ولدنا بها.
We should support each other
ينبغي علينا أن ندعم بعضنا البعض
and safeguard both the sanctuary and the mortal realm.
وصيانة الحرم والعالم الفاني.
Today, the sanctuary
اليوم الحرم
will hold the Wujing Saintess'
سوف تقام قديسة ووجينج
inspection ritual together.
طقوس التفتيش معًا.
Father, please grant me one more chance.
أبي، من فضلك امنحني فرصة أخرى.
If that is your wish,
إذا كانت هذه هي رغبتك،
then you and the elders
ثم أنت والشيوخ
shall travel to Wujing City to represent the sanctuary.
سوف يسافر إلى مدينة Wujing لتمثيل المحمية.
Watch Moshang complete
مشاهدة Moshang كاملة
the Wujing Saintess' inspection ritual as promised.
طقوس التفتيش الخاصة بقديسة وو جينغ كما وعدت.
No mistake is allowed.
لا يسمح بالخطأ.
It is my honor to offer my humble efforts
يشرفني أن أقدم جهودي المتواضعة
to the sanctuary.
الى الحرم.
I will ensure the ritual goes smoothly
سأضمن أن الطقوس تسير بسلاسة
to ease the burdens
لتخفيف الأعباء
of you and Moshang.
منك ومن موشانغ.
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
it's time to depart for War God's Hall.
لقد حان وقت المغادرة إلى قاعة إله الحرب.
Have you seen Zhilou?
هل رأيت زيلو؟
(Youyun Pavilion)
(جناح يويون)
I hope...
آمل...
everything goes well today.
كل شيء يسير على ما يرام اليوم.
I will await your return.
سأنتظر عودتك.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Moshang,
صباح الخير،
you don't look
أنت لا تبدو
very happy.
سعيدة جداً.
Oh, right. Where is that village girl you nearly died protecting?
أوه، صحيح. أين تلك الفتاة القروية التي كدت تموت لحمايتها؟
Did she not come to witness the ritual?
ولم تأت لتشهد الطقوس؟
I warn you.
أنا أحذرك.
Don't touch Feng Zhilou.
لا تلمس Feng Zhilou.
Moshang,
صباح الخير،
you are truly pitiful.
أنت حقا مثير للشفقة.
You stand so close to her,
أنت تقف قريبًا جدًا منها،
yet she has no right to stand by your side.
ولكن ليس لها الحق في الوقوف بجانبك.
In the end,
في النهاية،
you are destined to become another's husband.
أنت مقدر أن تصبح زوجًا لشخص آخر.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Struck a nerve?
هل أزعجتك؟
You're displeased?
هل أنت مستاء؟
Greetings, Your Highness.
تحياتي، صاحب السمو.
The Wujing Saintess' inspection ritual now begins!
بدأت الآن طقوس التفتيش الخاصة بقديسة وو جينغ !
It worked.
لقد نجحت.
Look.
ينظر.
Seems like
يبدو مثل
Princess Liluo of Wujing
الأميرة ليلو من Wujing
truly bears the Wujing Saintess' bloodline.
إنه يحمل حقًا سلالة القديسة وو جينغ.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
Elders,
الشيوخ،
the inspection ritual is complete.
تمت عملية التفتيش كاملة.
Princess Liluo of Wujing
الأميرة ليلو من Wujing
is indeed the Wujing Saintess' descendant.
هو في الواقع سليل القديسة وو جينغ.
In that case,
في هذه الحالة،
we shall return to the sanctuary
سوف نعود إلى الحرم
and begin preparations for my brother
وأبدأ الاستعدادات لأخي
and Princess Liluo's wedding.
وحفل زفاف الأميرة ليلو.
We kindly ask the sanctuary to oversee
نرجو من المحمية أن تشرف على
Liluo's wedding with His Highness.
حفل زفاف ليلو مع سموه.
(Why does she look exactly like my mother?)
(لماذا تشبه أمي تمامًا؟)
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Before we return to the sanctuary,
قبل أن نعود إلى الحرم،
I must resolve a question in my mind.
يجب أن أحل سؤالاً في ذهني.
This matter
هذه المسألة
concerns the safety of the sanctuary and the mortal realm.
يتعلق الأمر بسلامة الحرم والعالم البشري.
Li Yue,
لي يو,
at your age,
في عمرك،
how do you still look so young?
كيف لا تزال تبدو شابا جدا؟
Do none of you find this strange?
هل لا أحد منكم يجد هذا الأمر غريبا؟
I didn't think so before.
لم أكن أعتقد ذلك من قبل.
Now that he mentions it,
الآن بعد أن ذكر ذلك،
it seems quite strange.
يبدو غريباً جداً.
Right.
يمين.
He's right.
إنه على حق.
Your Highness, you know the truth.
صاحب السمو أنت تعرف الحقيقة.
It's because I carry the Wujing Saintess' bloodline
هذا لأنني أحمل سلالة القديسة وو جينغ
and have taken life-prolonging tonics for many years.
وقد تناولت المقويات التي تطيل العمر لسنوات عديدة.
Is it tonics...
هل هو منشطات...
or forbidden arts?
أو الفنون المحرمة؟
Moshang,
صباح الخير،
today is supposed to be your big day.
من المفترض أن يكون اليوم هو يومك الكبير.
Do you understand what you're saying?
هل تفهم ما تقوله؟
Today is just the Wujing Saintess' inspection ritual.
اليوم هو مجرد طقوس التفتيش للقديسة وو جينغ.
Where is this "big day" of mine?
أين هذا "اليوم الكبير" بالنسبة لي؟
Rongzhi,
رونغزي،
do you even understand
هل تفهم حتى؟
what you're saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
with the Wujing Saintess' bloodline
مع سلالة القديسة وو جينغ
and years of martial cultivation,
وسنوات من التدريب العسكري،
even as a human,
حتى كإنسان،
her lifespan
عمرها
far exceeds that of ordinary people.
يفوق بكثير ما لدى الناس العاديين.
Remaining youthful
البقاء شابا
for decades is normal.
منذ عقود من الزمن هو أمر طبيعي.
If you hadn't long consumed human blood
لو لم تستهلك الدم البشري لفترة طويلة
and used forbidden arts to preserve your looks,
واستخدمت الفنون المحرمة للحفاظ على مظهرك،
tainting yourself with blood poison,
تلويث نفسك بسم الدم،
you wouldn't look like a withered crone
لن تبدو مثل عجوز ذابلة
or suffer unbearable pain
أو تعاني من آلام لا تطاق
when the poison flares.
عندما يشتعل السم.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
She consumed human blood?
هل استهلكت دماء البشر؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
do not heed such rumors.
لا تلتفتوا لمثل هذه الشائعات
I stand before you healthy.
أقف أمامكم بصحة جيدة.
And Liluo
وليلوو
has been confirmed as the Wujing Saintess' descendant.
تم تأكيد أنه من نسل القديسة وو جينغ.
I am the Wujing City Lord.
أنا سيد مدينة ووجينج.
Why would I consume human blood?
لماذا أتناول الدم البشري؟
In truth, my visit here today
في الحقيقة زيارتي هنا اليوم
was not only to confirm
لم يكن فقط للتأكيد
the Wujing Saintess' identity.
هوية Wujing Saintess.
More importantly,
والأهم من ذلك،
I came to inform Wujing
لقد جئت لإبلاغ ووجينج
that I am canceling my engagement to Liluo.
أنني ألغي خطوبتي مع ليلو.
Moshang,
صباح الخير،
there are so many people here today.
هناك الكثير من الناس هنا اليوم.
Are you really announcing that you're ending your engagement,
هل تعلنين حقا أنك أنهيت خطوبتك؟
giving up marrying the Wujing Saintess,
التخلي عن الزواج من القديسة وو جينغ،
and abandoning your claim to the Dragon King's throne?
والتخلي عن مطالبتك بعرش ملك التنين؟
Marrying the Wujing Saintess
الزواج من قديسة ووجينج
was always the sanctuary's decision.
كان هذا دائمًا قرار الملجأ.
Don't forget the Dragon King's Decree.
لا تنسى مرسوم ملك التنين.
Only the Dragon Prince who weds the Wujing Saintess
فقط أمير التنين الذي يتزوج القديسة وو جينغ
can become the true Dragon King.
يمكن أن يصبح ملك التنين الحقيقي.
I'll say it again.
سأقولها مرة أخرى.
Whether I marry the Wujing Saintess
هل أتزوج من القديسة وو جينغ؟
has nothing to do with whether I'm worthy
لا علاقة له بكوني جديرًا
of becoming Dragon King or whether
من أن يصبح ملك التنين أو ما إذا كان
I can save the sanctuary and all life
أستطيع أن أنقذ الحرم وكل الحياة
in the world.
في العالم.
Chu Moshang,
تشو موشانغ،
you acted on your own,
لقد تصرفت بمفردك،
disrupting the union between the sanctuary and Wujing.
تعطيل الاتحاد بين الحرم وووجينج.
How do you plan to answer
كيف تخطط للإجابة؟
to us and to the Dragon King?
لنا وللملك التنين؟
I will
أنا سوف
return to the sanctuary
العودة إلى الحرم
and explain everything to Father.
وأشرح كل شيء للأب.
You need not worry.
لا داعي للقلق.
Very well.
جيد جدا.
Moshang,
صباح الخير،
you said it yourself.
لقد قلت ذلك بنفسك.
When the time comes,
عندما يحين الوقت،
don't blame me for being ruthless.
لا تلوموني على كوني قاسيًا.
Why...
لماذا...
Why is this happening?
لماذا يحدث هذا؟
I have already passed
لقد مررت بالفعل
the inspection ritual.
طقوس التفتيش.
Why did the Dragon Princes leave?
لماذا غادر أمراء التنين؟
Why would Prince Shang give up
لماذا يستسلم الأمير شانغ؟
his engagement to me?
خطوبته لي؟
Give me an explanation!
أعطني تفسيرا!
Elders,
الشيوخ،
is this the sanctuary's idea
هل هذه فكرة الحرم؟
of sincerity toward Wujing?
من الصدق تجاه Wujing؟
Breaking your word
كسر كلمتك
and toying with us like this?
ويلعب معنا بهذه الطريقة؟
This is an emergency.
هذه حالة طارئة.
Just wait for news from the sanctuary.
فقط انتظر الأخبار من المحمية.
Elders,
الشيوخ،
for the sake of the sanctuary
من أجل الحرم
and the future of the mortal realm,
ومستقبل العالم البشري،
you would not dare go against
لن تجرؤ على الذهاب ضد
the Dragon King's Decree, would you?
مرسوم ملك التنين، هل توافق؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Elders!
الشيوخ!
My lord!
سيدي!
She fainted from shock.
لقد أغمي عليها من الصدمة.
Send her back to the Longevity Hall.
أرسلها مرة أخرى إلى قاعة طول العمر.
You wretch! How dare you disregard the safety of the sanctuary
يا لك من حقير! كيف تجرؤ على تجاهل سلامة الحرم؟
and the mortal realm?
والعالم البشري؟
On your knees!
على ركبتيك!
Father,
أب،
every word I said is true.
كل كلمة قلتها صحيحة.
Li Yue's strange illness
مرض لي يوي الغريب
has worsened over the past 18 years.
وقد تفاقمت الأمور على مدى السنوات الثماني عشرة الماضية.
Those who served her and treated her
الذين خدموها وعالجوها
have died one after another.
ماتوا واحدا تلو الآخر.
The physician closest to her
الطبيب الأقرب لها
is a mute girl.
هي فتاة خرساء.
I sent you to the mortal realm to retrieve the sigil
لقد أرسلتك إلى عالم البشر لاستعادة الرمز
and verify the Wujing Saintess' bloodline.
والتحقق من سلالة القديسة وو جينغ.
Not to meddle
لا للتدخل
in the petty schemes of the Humans.
في المخططات التافهة للبشر.
If every human dispute
إذا كان كل نزاع إنساني
required our intervention,
تطلب تدخلنا،
why would the heavens grant power
لماذا تمنح السماوات القوة؟
to us Dragons?
لنا التنانين؟
Father,
أب،
this concerns the Dragon King's Decree.
هذا يتعلق بمرسوم ملك التنين.
What does it
ماذا يعني ذلك
have to do with Li Yue's illness?
هل له علاقة بمرض لي يوي؟
Or with your refusal to marry?
أم مع رفضك الزواج؟
Wujing City Lord, Li Yue,
لورد مدينة ووجينج، لي يو
is not of the Wujing Saintess' bloodline.
ليست من سلالة القديسة وو جينغ.
That is why
لهذا السبب
she suffers from blood poisoning.
إنها تعاني من تسمم الدم.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
then Liluo is not the Wujing Saintess.
إذاً فإن ليلو ليست قديسة وو جينغ.
Moshang,
صباح الخير،
we've all witnessed
لقد شهدنا جميعا
the verification
التحقق
of Princess Liluo's identity
هوية الأميرة ليلو
as the Wujing Saintess that day.
مثل قديسة وو جينغ في ذلك اليوم.
Now you're denying it
الآن أنت تنكر ذلك
and making up such a bizarre excuse?
واختلاق مثل هذا العذر الغريب؟
This isn't just about refusing the marriage, is it?
لا يتعلق الأمر فقط برفض الزواج، أليس كذلك؟
Is this
هذا هو
for your beloved,
لحبيبك
Feng Zhilou?
فنغ تشيلو؟
I merely did what I believe is right.
لقد فعلت فقط ما أعتقد أنه صحيح.
Princess Liluo
الأميرة ليلو
lacks virtue.
يفتقر إلى الفضيلة.
She is cruel and violent.
إنها قاسية وعنيفة.
She is unfit to bear
إنها غير صالحة للتحمل
the title of Wujing Saintess.
لقب القديسة ووجينج.
We Dragons
نحن التنانين
can never take such a woman as Dragon Queen.
لا يمكن أبدًا أن أقبل امرأة مثل ملكة التنين.
Seems like
يبدو مثل
you want both Feng Zhilou
تريد كلا من Feng Zhilou
and the Dragon King's throne.
وعرش ملك التنين.
Are you going to say
هل ستقول
that the real Wujing Saintess
أن القديسة ووجينج الحقيقية
is Feng Zhilou?
هل هو فنغ تشيلو؟
Stop fanning the flames.
توقف عن تأجيج النيران.
Whoever Feng Zhilou is
من هو فنغ تشيلو
and whoever the Wujing Saintess may be,
وأيا كانت قديسة وو جينغ،
the only one I long for
الوحيد الذي أشتاق إليه
is Feng Zhilou.
هو فنغ تشيلو.
Then today's inspection ritual
ثم طقوس التفتيش اليوم
has become nothing but a joke.
لقد أصبح مجرد مزحة.
Shang,
شانغ،
marry Liluo
تزوج ليلو
and inherit the Dragon King's throne,
ويرث عرش ملك التنين،
or be with Feng Zhilou, that human girl.
أو كن مع فينج تشيلو، تلك الفتاة البشرية.
You can choose only one.
يمكنك اختيار واحد فقط.
Father,
أب،
if inheriting the throne
إذا ورث العرش
means marrying Liluo,
يعني الزواج من ليلو
then I would rather give up the throne.
إذن أفضل أن أتخلى عن العرش.
I placed great hopes on you.
لقد وضعت عليك آمالا كبيرة.
You're shouldering the fate of us Dragons
أنت تتحمل مصيرنا نحن التنانين
and the lives of all living beings.
وحياة جميع الكائنات الحية.
Father,
أب،
have you ever considered
هل فكرت يوما
what the Wujing Saintess truly represents?
ماذا تمثل القديسة وو جينغ حقًا؟
In ancient times, was she also
في العصور القديمة، كانت أيضًا
nothing more than a tool
ليس أكثر من مجرد أداة
to be married off to us?
أن تتزوج منا؟
Could a marriage alliance really summon the Dragon King's Decree,
هل يمكن لتحالف الزواج أن يستدعي حقًا مرسوم ملك التنين،
restore the sanctuary's barrier,
استعادة حاجز الحرم،
and save the world?
وإنقاذ العالم؟
I don't care who the Wujing Saintess is.
لا يهمني من هي القديسة وو جينغ.
I care only for the barrier.
أنا أهتم فقط بالحاجز.
Liluo's bloodline has already been verified.
لقد تم التحقق من سلالة ليلو بالفعل.
She is the Wujing Saintess.
هي قديسة ووجينج.
That means she can fulfill
وهذا يعني أنها قادرة على الوفاء
the Dragon King's prophecy. That is enough.
نبوءة ملك التنين. هذا يكفي.
I will ask you once more.
سأسألك مرة أخرى.
Are you sure you want to give up
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد الاستسلام؟
the Dragon King's throne
عرش ملك التنين
for an ordinary human girl?
لفتاة بشرية عادية؟
Father,
أب،
the throne was never what I wanted.
العرش لم يكن ما أردته أبدًا.
What I want is to fail neither the people nor you.
ما أريده هو أن لا أخذل الناس ولا أنت.
Moshang,
صباح الخير،
you may have given Feng Zhilou
ربما تكون قد أعطيت فينج تشيلو
the sanctuary's sigil and the Fire Phoenix pendant,
رمز الحرم وقلادة طائر الفينيق الناري،
but you cannot disregard
ولكن لا يمكنك تجاهل
the Dragon King's Decree for her.
مرسوم ملك التنين لها.
By doing so, you place our sanctuary
ومن خلال القيام بذلك، فإنك تضع ملاذنا
and the mortal realm in danger.
والعالم البشري في خطر.
Young Master,
السيد الشاب،
you actually gave Feng Zhilou
لقد أعطيت في الواقع Feng Zhilou
the Fire Phoenix pendant too?
قلادة فينيكس الناري أيضا؟
Yes.
نعم.
The Fire Phoenix pendant
قلادة طائر الفينيق الناري
is the token a Dragon Prince gives his wife.
هو الرمز الذي يعطيه أمير التنين لزوجته.
It belongs to me.
إنها ملكي.
I can give it to whomever I choose.
أستطيع أن أعطيها لمن أختار.
Besides,
بجانب،
Feng Zhilou is no ordinary girl.
فينج تشيلو ليست فتاة عادية.
She is the one I have chosen as my wife.
إنها من اخترتها زوجة لي.
Calm down, Father.
اهدأ يا أبي.
Moshang was just like that in the mortal realm.
كان موشانغ تمامًا مثل ذلك في عالم البشر.
He rejected the marriage in public, abandoned the Saintess,
رفض الزواج علانية، وتخلى عن القديسة،
and disgraced Wujing City.
وإهانة مدينة ووجينج.
And now he dares defy me as well.
والآن يجرؤ على تحديني أيضًا.
I believe Moshang acts this way today
أعتقد أن موشانغ يتصرف بهذه الطريقة اليوم
only because he was blinded
فقط لأنه كان أعمى
by Feng Zhilou saving his life.
بواسطة فينج تشيلو ينقذ حياته.
Our top priority now
أولويتنا القصوى الآن
is to calm Wujing City
هو تهدئة مدينة ووجينج
and continue the alliance between us.
ومواصلة التحالف بيننا.
I'll leave the matters of Wujing City to you.
سأترك لك أمور مدينة ووجينج.
Don't disappoint me.
لا تخيب ظني.
Yes, Father.
نعم يا أبي.
I endured all this suffering
لقد تحملت كل هذا المعاناة
to marry a Dragon.
الزواج من التنين.
And what did I get in return?
وماذا حصلت في المقابل؟
Public humiliation.
الإذلال العلني.
Your Grace,
صاحب السمو،
nothing is decided yet.
لم يتم تحديد أي شيء بعد.
Though Prince Shang acted impulsively,
على الرغم من أن الأمير شانغ تصرف بشكل متهور،
as long as the Dragon King remains,
طالما بقي ملك التنين،
this marriage, meant for all life in the world,
هذا الزواج، المخصص لجميع أشكال الحياة في العالم،
must be fulfilled.
يجب أن تتحقق.
But haven't you seen
ولكن ألم ترى
that he is starting to suspect
أنه بدأ يشك
Mother's blood poisoning?
تسمم دم الأم؟
But today, you have proven before all
لكن اليوم أثبتم أمام الجميع
your bloodline as the Wujing Saintess.
سلالة دمك كقديسة وو جينغ.
Next, we just need to quickly finalize the marriage.
والآن، كل ما نحتاجه هو الانتهاء سريعاً من الزواج.
Everything will be settled.
كل شيء سوف يتم تسويته.
Who could possibly go back on it?
من يمكنه الرجوع عن ذلك؟
It seems I have been far too soft-hearted.
يبدو أنني كنت طيب القلب للغاية.
I should have had Feng Zhilou killed
كان ينبغي لي أن أقتل فينج تشيلو
before she entered Wujing City.
قبل دخولها مدينة ووجينج.
Feng Zhilou must not be killed.
لا ينبغي أن يُقتل فينج تشيلو.
Yue's power as the Wujing Saintess
قوة يو باعتبارها Wujing Saintess
is pitifully weak now.
إنه ضعيف بشكل مثير للشفقة الآن.
Feng Zhilou
فنغ تشيلو
is your spare blood vessel.
هو وعاء الدم الاحتياطي لديك.
She must not be killed?
لا ينبغي قتلها؟
She must not be killed,
لا ينبغي قتلها،
so I must let her walk over me?
فهل يجب أن أسمح لها بالسير فوقي؟
Once I become the Dragon Queen,
بمجرد أن أصبح ملكة التنين،
I will have her turned into a dried corpse
سأحولها إلى جثة جافة
to vent my frustration.
لتنفيس عن إحباطي.
Inform Chu Xiaoyu
أبلغ تشو شياو يو
to prepare the blood-restoring tonic
لتحضير منشط استعادة الدم
and come with me to the dungeon.
وتأتي معي إلى الزنزانة.
That wicked woman is truly hateful.
هذه المرأة الشريرة مكروهة حقا.
Zhilou,
جيلو،
you have formidable martial skills.
لديك مهارات قتالية هائلة.
Just storm in
فقط اقتحم
and rescue your mother.
وأنقذ والدتك.
I can't.
لا أستطبع.
Even if I fight my way
حتى لو قاتلت في طريقي
through the heavily guarded dungeon,
من خلال الزنزانة المحروسة بشدة،
taking my mother out with me
أخذ والدتي معي
would be difficult.
سيكون صعبا.
She has no martial skill now,
ليس لديها أي مهارة قتالية الآن،
and her mind is clouded.
وعقلها غائم.
She could easily be harmed.
من الممكن أن تتعرض للأذى بسهولة.
I can't take even the slightest risk.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل حتى أدنى مخاطرة.
Then what shall we do?
ثم ماذا نفعل؟
Just watch helplessly
فقط شاهد بلا حول ولا قوة
as your mother
مثل أمك
is bullied by that wicked woman?
هل يتم التنمر عليه من قبل تلك المرأة الشريرة؟
The Dragon Prince
أمير التنين
rejected the marriage publicly at the War God's Hall.
رفض الزواج علنًا في قاعة إله الحرب.
Liluo will surely draw blood again.
من المؤكد أن ليلو سوف يسحب الدم مرة أخرى.
Let's enter the dungeon again.
دعونا ندخل الزنزانة مرة أخرى.
(Liluo told me to prepare the tonic)
(طلب مني ليلو أن أحضر التونيك)
(and go to the dungeon with her.)
(واذهب معها إلى الزنزانة.)
♪Like petals fall, gone with the clouds♪
♪مثل البتلات المتساقطة، ذهبت مع السحب♪
♪Like stars fade fast in open skies♪
♪مثل النجوم تتلاشى بسرعة في السماء المفتوحة♪
♪Like snowflakes melting softly in the evening haze♪
♪مثل رقاقات الثلج التي تذوب برفق في ضباب المساء♪
♪Like your fleeting glance that gave me one brief dream's grace♪
♪مثل نظرتك العابرة التي منحتني نعمة حلم قصير♪
♪Like fireflies flicker through wild grass, fleeting light♪
♪مثل اليراعات التي تومض عبر العشب البري، ضوء عابر♪
♪Like evening breeze that stirs soft hair in twilight♪
♪مثل نسيم المساء الذي يحرك الشعر الناعم في الشفق♪
♪Like fleeting thoughts that surge and then unwind♪
♪مثل الأفكار العابرة التي تتدفق ثم تتلاشى♪
♪Chance meetings fade, just empty rooms left behind♪
♪تتلاشى اللقاءات العرضية، وتبقى الغرف الفارغة فقط♪
♪You brought a wave that stirred a wild, restless sea♪
♪لقد جلبت موجة أثارت بحرًا هائجًا لا يهدأ♪
♪Light as a feather, yet it sank an island deep in me♪
♪خفيفة كالريشة، لكنها غرقت في جزيرة عميقة في داخلي♪
♪In that one moment, life's grip I couldn't break or sway♪
♪في تلك اللحظة، لم أستطع كسر قبضة الحياة أو التخلص منها♪
♪Leaving me lost in memories, small and fading away♪
♪تركني ضائعًا في الذكريات، صغيرة وتتلاشى♪